字
字幕
字幕製
字幕製作
字幕製作 ★
字幕製作 ★ 至
字幕製作 ★ 至宏
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上人
超危險特工2 狠戰
Baby, check this out.
寶貝，過來看看這個
A power washer?
吸塵器？
We need one of these.
我們需要一台
Yeah.
哦
On the patio in the backyard.
在後院的天台
Yeah.
哦
Should we go look at those window treatments?
我們該去看看窗簾嗎
No.
不
Do you want one of these hotdogs?
吃根熱狗怎麼樣？
They're vey good.
很好吃的
Baby, you are a heck of a homemaker.
寶貝，你真是個好家庭主夫
You know that?
你知道嗎？
But we could just go to dinner.
其實我們可以到外面吃
Well, you know...
嗯，你知道…
if you don't make it...
如果你不做飯…
You don't eat it.
你不吃的話
You know what? That's a great idea.
這主意還是不錯的
What if I make you dinner?
我給你做晚餐怎麼樣？
I'm gonna go and get that grill. The big shiny one.
我去選一些新鮮的烤肉
Will you get us some shrimp? The big jumbo kind.
你去選幾隻大蝦，好嗎
4 down. 3 over.
直走，在第三區
Come back and find me down here. In tools.
回來時我會都選好在購物籃裏
What the hell are you doing here?
你在這裏幹什麼？
You ignored my messages.
你沒回我的信息
I am happy.
我很快樂
You're desperate.
你很絕望
I can make this work.
我能完成這項任務
You're playing house.
法蘭克，你在玩家家酒
Look, I'm retired. I'm happy. We are happy.
聽著，我退休了，我很高興，我們很幸福
Frank...
法蘭克…
You haven't killed anybody in months.
已經好幾個月沒有殺人了
That is not a bad thing.
這不是件壞事，對嗎
That's a positive thing for a lot of people.
對很多人來說
Kemosabe, I need you. They're coming. I can feel it.
我需要你，他們就要來了，我有預感
You are driving me nuts, Marvin.
這是要把我逼瘋了，馬文
If it makes you feel better, bring the girl.
把那女孩一起帶來，可能你會好受點
I'm not gonna bring the girl anmhere.
我才不會帶上她
Don't bring the girl where?
不帶女孩去哪裏？
We're just catching up.
因為恰巧
What is it?
什麼？
Marvin's here. I just bumped into Marvin.
碰到馬文，我跟他聊了一下
Where are we going?
我們要去哪裏？
No, come on. They're gonna close.
不早了他們要打烊了
Good to see you, Marvin.
很高興見到你，馬文
Good to see you.
很高興見到你
Frank.
法蘭克
You know you want to.
你知道你想的
No.
不
Come on.
來吧
Last chance, Frank.
最後的機會，法蘭克
I'm taking Sarah home.
我帶莎拉回家去
Stay safe.
小心
Well, I really wanted to be...
我真的想…
Of course, it is, honey.
當然，寶貝
You are never gonna be in danger ever again.
你再也不會身陷險地了，不會了
We don't even know what happened.
我們甚至不知道發生什麼事了
We don't know who's in there.
我們都不知道誰在那裏
How am I gonna protect you?
我到底該如何保護你？
Hey. He was your best friend.
嘿，他是你最好的朋友
Come on.
不是嗎
Wow.
哇
He still looks so lifelike.
他還是那麼栩栩如生
He's not dead.
好像仍然活著
Don't do that. Just let your feelings out.
不要這樣，把感傷發洩出來
No. Really.
不，真的
He does this a lot.
他經常這麼做
Really?
對嗎？
No, come on. Give me the pin.
不要這樣，把針給我
Come on, sweetie. Let's go sit down.
來吧，親愛的，快坐下
I should kiss him.
我應該先親他的
Go ahead. Do you want to?
你要就去吧？
Let's go sit down. Come on, sweetie.
讓我們坐下，來吧，親愛的
At this time, we'll open the floor to anyone...
這一刻，我們將開放…
who wishes to say a few words about the deceased.
希望有人對死者說幾句話
Babe...
寶貝…
Share a memoy, perhaps?
分享回憶？
Perhaps, a poem. A song lyric.
或者詠詩，或歌曲
Anyone?
誰來？
You can do it.
你可以的
Sir?
先生？
Marvin was...
馬文…
different.
與眾不同
He was...
他…
a vey good shot.
一個好人
Some would say that...
有人說…
he was paranoid.
他很偏執
But you have to expect a little of that...
但是你也能想到些…
when the CIA's dosing you with LSD...
因為中情局給了LSD…
for a little more than a decade.
差不多十年了
He could wire a bomb...
他可以引爆一個炸彈…
faster than anybody I ever met.
比任何人都要快
The good people of Moldova will always...
我所知道的人當中…
be in Marvin's debt.
馬文是最好的
He was a really good friend.
他是個真正的好朋友
Really good.
真的很好
I'm gonna miss him.
我會懷念他的
Gonna miss him.
會想念他的
We have to move.
我們該走了
Canada?
加拿大？
High ground. Good kill zones. It's a little farm.
離開這危險之地，那裏有個小農場
A farm? Like, to farm on?
農場？像耕農一樣？
Like, with crops?
像種小麥？
Yeah. It could be fun.
是啊，很有趣
Listen, babe...
聽著，寶貝…
You know they say it's really important not to make big...
你要知道人們常說，重要的是經過…
life altering decisions right after a loss.
危難之後才會做出選擇
If they can get to Marvin, they can get to you and they can get to me.
他們可以殺了馬文，也可以殺了你或我
Who are they?
他們是誰？
Go to the safe house.
到安全的地方去
Look at me.
看著我
Go to the safe house.
到安全的地方去
I'll come find you.
我會去找你的
I'm not leaving you.
我不會離開你的
It'll be All right.
真的沒事的
What is it?
這是什麼？
Mr. Moses...
摩西先生…
They want to debrief you at a Yankee White facility.
他們要你做一份白揚基的匯報
Is that your sniper?
是你的狙擊手嗎？
You're flagged Retired E_remely Dangerous.
你是認為是『危險退休人員』
白揚基
Hi there.
你好
My client Frank Moses is here.
我的客戶法蘭克·摩西是在這裏
He's an American citizen being detained illegally without due process.
他是美國公民，未經正當程序被非法拘留
You know what? That is a lovely blazer.
可愛的夾克
Oh, Thank you.
謝謝
You're welcome.
不客氣
I'm sorry, I have no idea.
抱歉，我不知道
But let me get Mr. Snyder for you.
讓我幫你打給斯奈德先生
Thank you.
謝謝
How can I help you?
嗨，你的名字是？
Hi there. What is your name?
嘿，你叫什麼名字？
John Snyder.
約翰·斯奈德
John. I didn't get your name.
約翰，我不知道你的名字
It's Kelly.
凱莉
Hi, Kelly.
嗨，凱莉
John...
約翰…
John... John!
約翰…約翰！
Unless you want to end up like Kelly...
除非你想像凱莉一樣…
I suggest you tell me where Frank Moses is right now.
你最好告訴我法蘭克在哪裏
Now!
快點！
In interrogation.
審問室
I got a document right here that says that...
資料裏顯示…
you have a special interest in the Cold War.
你對冷戰有特殊的興趣
We know that back in the day, you spent a lotta time in Russia.
我們知道你在俄羅斯那段糟糕的事
I just need to know what you know about Project Nightshade.
我想知道你所瞭解的『暗影行動』
I really don't know anything about it.
我一無所知
What the hell is that?
怎麼了？
Small arms gunfire, 200 yards.
襲擊者來了，還有200碼
Watch him.
看著他
100 yards.
100碼
They're coming to kill us.
他們是來殺我們的
Get me outta these cuffs.
打開手銬
I can't do that, sir.
我不能，先生
You have the key, right?
你有鑰匙，對吧？
Hands up!
舉起手來！
50 feet.
50英尺
They're gonna kill us both, if you don't get me outta these cuffs.
如果不打開手銬，他們會殺了我們
Come on.
快點
Frank Moses.
法蘭克·摩西
Coming up through the ranks, you were my hero.
你可是我心目中的大英雄
Given enough time, I guess eveyone cracks.
時間充足，每個人都會受不了
Frank.
法蘭克
Who are you?
你是誰？
Me?
我嗎？
I'm the guy the government hires to get information.
我是政府僱用收集情報的
And I'm allowed to use any form of torture I deem fit.
我為求情報不擇手段
And I will torture Sarah until you speak.
我打算折磨莎拉，直到你開口
Speaking of Sarah...
提到莎拉…
I love watching her...
我喜歡看著她…
shave her legs in the tub.
在浴缸裏掙扎的樣子
Kinda reminds me of these Belgian mercs I met in the Congo.
令我想起了剛果叛軍
They would skin people alive to get them to talk.
他們為了情報而活剝人的皮膚
And do you know where they started?
你知道他們在哪裏開始的嗎？
Guess.
猜猜看
At the ankles. Just like your Sarah.
腳踝，就像你的莎拉一樣
So...
所以…
you either give me the information that I need to know...
給我滿意的答案…
Or I'm gonna filet your girl from head to toe with no mercy.
否則對你的女友毫不留情
Awesome.
真棒啊
Wow.
哇
Pretty good for a retired guy. But are you
退休真好，但是你
1234567...
1，2，3，4，5，6，7…
7 on 1 cuffed with no weapon good?
來吧，七個對一個手無寸鐵的人？
Son of a.
混蛋
Go. Go go go!
向前，走，走，走！
Shoot him, but don't kill him.
向他開槍，但別殺了他
All right, kill him. Spray it up.
好了，殺掉他吧，散開
Frank, this is your last chance.
法蘭克，這是你最後的機會
Fire.
射擊
Get in there! Go!
進去！快！
Shit.
媽的
Marvin!
馬文！
You're driving me crazy!
你把我逼瘋了！
I brought the key.
我帶鑰匙來了
You faked your death.
你騙我你死了
Gotta go.
我們該走了
Let's go.
走吧
Gotta go.
快走
You have no idea what you put me through!
我現在該怎麼辦
Thank God, you're okay.
感謝老天爺，你沒事
No!
不！
What are you doing here?
你在這裏幹什麼？
Marvin brought me. From the house.
馬文從那屋子把我帶出來
Has eveybody lost their mind?
大家都瘋了嗎？
You don't bring a girl like that here.
你怎麼能把一個女孩帶到這裏
I had to see if you were okay.
我必須確認你沒事
Honey!
甜心！
I thought...
我以為…
What?
什麼？
Remember when we discussed how you were gonna lay low?
我不是說過要低調點嗎？
You don't get to tell me when to lay.
你又沒有告訴我到何時為止
I'm not saying that.
我是沒有這麼說
Stop. Just don't.
止住，就停住
You're mad at me now?
你現在要對我發飆嗎？
You treat me like a China doll.
你一直像對玩偶一樣耍我
Frank, can I give you a little advice about women?
法蘭克，我能給你一點忠告嗎？
Absolutely not!
當然不！
Ask yourself, what is a girl like that doing with a guy like you?
你捫心自問一下，什麼樣的女孩喜歡你這種傢伙？
It ain't for your looks.
這不是你的樣子
I will shoot you. I will shoot you in the liver.
我會射你，我會射掉你的肝臟
A, R, D, A.
A，R，D，A
Adventure, romance, danger...
冒險、浪漫、危險…
activities you can share as a couple.
活動，你們可以是一對搭擋
It's about you lying to me.
是因為你騙了我
Frank...
法蘭克…
I was vey touched that you cried at my funeral.
我很感動你在我的葬禮上哭
That's not true.
你錯了
I didn't cy at your funeral.
我根本沒有哭
I'm no crier.
我沒有哭
96 hours ago, somebody posted a document on the Internet...
96小時，有人在網上洩露文件…
that said you and I took part in an operation called Nightshade...
提到我與你參與的『暗影行動』…
back in '79.
在79年時
That's why you fake died?
所以你裝死嗎？
Yeah. The chatter went through the roof.
是啊，嘮叨的快撐破屋頂了
So eveybody's after you...
所以老是很多人追你…
for something they think you know that you don't even know at all?
問你一些你不知道的事情？
Oh my God! Spiders!
喔，天啊！蜘蛛！
Honey, you need to go to ground and it's best I don't know where.
親愛的，你最好藏到我不知道的地方
Yeah, I'm not going anmhere.
我哪裏也不去
Cash only. No calls.
只用現金，不能打電話
No contacts.
不要聯繫
Thanks. Look...
謝謝，聽著…
I'm not hanging out in some bunker...
我不會躲在安樂窩裏…
while you slink around and save the planet...
當你在外面一邊與深膚色的性感女人鬼混…
with dusky international femme fatales.
一邊去拯救世界
Dusky?
深膚色的性感女人
Dark, smoldering.
膚色性感，火辣
I know what it means. Marvin.
我知道那是什麼意思，馬文
It's hard to be the kinda person I have to be right now...
我現在的處境很危險…
and do the kinda things that I'm going to have to do...
要做的事情也很困難…
while you're here.
而你在這裏
This is gonna be good for us.
這對我們都不是很好
What are we doing?
我們要怎麼做？
Face it, Columbo, things were getting a little stale.
我們面對它，科倫坡，讓事情可以控制
Wow. Mommy just slapped Daddy at the dinner table.
哇，媽媽在餐桌上揍了老爹
Is there a human being in the trunk?
是有人在後車箱嗎？
Yeah.
是啊
Who is it? Marvin.
是誰呢？馬文
He's a Senior Director of Militay Intelligence.
一個高級軍事情報指揮官
I've been caramelizing his onions for a couple of days.
我已經被折磨好幾天了
Caramelizing how?
怎麼折磨呢？
With three tabs of acid and a lot of rats.
迷幻藥，還有一些老鼠
Dang!
媽啊！
五角大廈
11 people dead.
11個人被殺
5 FBI.
5個FBI的
And the SecDef wants a briefing?
要跟國防部怎麼報告？
You were brought in to contain this.
你是罪魁禍首
Calm down.
冷靜點
I can't believe this is coming back on me after so many years.
我無法相信事隔多年故事又重演了
General, Moses and Boggs have been completely isolated.
將軍，摩西和博格斯，已經被完全孤立
The FBI is seeking them for the murders.
FBI正以謀殺罪搜捕他們
Homeland has been informed that they are officially domestic terrorists.
國安局把他們列為恐怖份子
Is that gonna work?
這樣可行嗎？
Yes.
是的
The problem is with that document su_acing on the Internet...
問題是，如果文件在網路上流傳…
all the players will be coming after Nightshade.
所有參加『暗影行動』的人將曝光
It'll open the book on this.
這事可能會被史書記載
I'm calling SecDef. We need to go public.
我去國防部一趟，我們要公諸大眾
General...
將軍…
Nobody's going public.
任何人都不行公佈
We need a new plan for Moses.
對摩西我們要有個計劃
I need you to approve a specialist.
我須要你制定一個專案
What? CIA?
什麼？CIA嗎？
It's been tried, sir. Didn't work so well for those guys.
試試吧，長官，千萬別交給這些人
Han Cho Bai. He's the best.
韓卓佰，他是最佳人選
Do it.
就這樣
香港
Suit, too.
襯衫也要
He's clean.
他很安全
Seriously?
這是幹嘛？
Sit down, Mr. Han.
請坐，韓先生
Your security is impressive.
你的安全措施很完備
A business associate.
此次的目標人物
Julio Alvarez Fernandes.
胡里奧、瓦雷斯、費南茲
Vey difficult to get close to.
他很難接近
Of course, it must appear like an accident.
當然，必須做得像意外事件
Not a problem. Except for one thing.
沒有問題，除了一件事
Mr. Fernandes pays better.
費南茲先生，付了更多的費用
Yeah?
是？
Who's the target?
目標是誰？
It's an old pal of yours. Frank Moses.
你的老友，法蘭克·摩西
Karma's a bitch, Frank.
他媽的老混蛋，法蘭克
MI6總部-倫敦
What is this?
怎麼了？
There's a watchword flag on a WikiLeaks document.
這是維基百科上的文件
It's coded Priority One Alpha Seven.
它的優先代碼是，1-Alpha-7
Something called Nightshade.
叫做『暗影行動』
Shut up!
住嘴！
Get out.
出去
Find me Victoria Winslow.
替我找維多利亞·溫斯洛
Director Philips?
菲利普長官？
I'm with someone right now.
我現在和某人在一起
Keeping busy, I see.
我知道你很忙
Idle hands do the Devil's work.
只是些骯髒的工作而已
Yes.
是啊
I understand you can get close to Frank Moses.
我知道你能接近法蘭克·摩西
Yes.
是的
MI6 has a iob for you.
MI6有個任務給你
If you want to stay alive, you're going to accept it.
如果你想活命，就必須接受
It's time to choose sides, Victoria.
是時候選邊站了，維多利亞
Where do they teach you guys this stuff?
誰教你們這些的？
Manuals, mostly.
使用手冊
Some of this stuff you just can't teach.
有些事是不用教的
Wow.
哇
Isn't this cool?
很酷啊？
We're on a mission together.
我們一起執行任務
Do you have any idea how many people are tying to kill us?
你知道嗎？有很多人想幹掉我們
We both know this is where you belong.
我們都知道這是你的地盤
Right here. In the thick of it.
就在這裏
Pussy Cat's right, Frank.
她說得對，法蘭克
Here we go.
走吧
Watch your step.
腳下留神
Come on!
幫幫忙！
Where did you get this?
你從哪裏拿的？
Marvin.
馬文
You gave her a gun?
你給她槍？
It is America.
這裏是美國
Eveyone else has a gun.
每個人都可以有槍
She has no idea what to do with this.
她不會使用它
I know exactly what to do with it.
我知道怎麼用
You don't give fire to a kitten.
你不能給小貓一把槍
Why don't you just give her some dynamite?
為什麼不給她一些炸藥？
No exernal safety on the Sig?
手槍沒有開保險嗎？
Tell him what you told me.
告訴他我對你說的
At the height of the Cold War...
在冷戰的時候…
Nightshade was cooked up by a rogue US General...
暗影行動是一個美國將軍制定的…
as a first strike capability against the Soviets.
第一目標是對抗蘇聯
That's it. Can I go?
就這樣，我可以走了嗎？
You want a little pepper with that?
想要再來點辣椒嗎？
At the height of the Cold War...
冷戰時期…
a megaton yield device was smuggled into Moscow...
大量設備走私到莫斯科…
in diplomatic pouches, piece by piece...
用外交郵件，一件一件的…
and then the weapon was lost. That's it.
可是武器消失不見了，就這樣
You lost a nuke in Moscow?
你在莫斯科弄丟了武器？
The scientist was Edward Bailey. That's it.
那科學家叫，愛德華·貝利，就是他
What?
怎麼了？
I made a mistake.
我犯了個錯
Edward Bailey was a genius physicist...
愛德華·貝利是個天才物理學家…
who built some of the greatest stuff during the Cold War.
冷戰時最大的武器是他製造的
Neutron bombs, particle beam weapons, nerve gas.
中子炸彈、粒子束武器、神經毒氣
Excellent nerve gas.
特別是神經毒氣
He was a rock star of conceptual mass killing.
他是暗殺界的閃亮之星
They called him "The Da Vinci of Death".
他們稱他為『達芬奇之死』
We were the security detail...
我們那時執行武器安檢…
assigned to getting him in and out of Moscow safely.
試圖把它安全移出莫斯科
What happened?
發生什麼事了？
We thought he was secure.
我們以為萬無一失時
The Soviets got him with a car bomb.
蘇聯軍隊在一輛炸彈汽車抓到了他
It was my fault.
都是我的錯
He's dead.
他死了
Run or fight?
逃跑還是戰鬥？
All we've got is this WikiLeaks page off the Internet.
我們得到的只是維基百科的網頁
Out of a Paris IP.
來自巴黎的IP
Paris could be anybody.
巴黎的任何一個人
Wait. Scroll back down for a second.
等等，回去前面去
What is that?
那是什麼？
Coffee stain?
咖啡污點？
Wine.
酒
Frog.
青蛙
What?
怎麼了？
We're okay.
沒事
Your number.
你的電話
Yeah.
是
MI6 has just given me a contract to kill you.
MI6剛剛給我一個任務去殺你
Apparently, you're guilty of nuclear terrorism, murder...
核子武器的罪魁禍首…
and you're number one on Interpol's Most Wanted.
第一首要的通緝犯
What did you say?
你怎麼說呢？
I said "Yes."
我說『好啊』
The money's good. And if I don't do it, somebody else will.
你知道報酬優厚，我不做別人也會做的
You should know the Americans are sending someone also.
你要知道美國也派人在搜尋你
Who?
誰呢？
Han.
韓
It's bad, isn't it?
很糟糕，不是嗎？
Is that Marvin?
那是馬文嗎？
Yes. And Sarah.
是的，還有莎拉
Send them my love.
幫我向她問好
They're driving me crazy.
他們把我快逼瘋了
Marvin gave her a gun.
馬文給了她一支槍
Was it loaded?
有子彈嗎？
Yes!
有！
Are you being controlling?
你能控制住嗎？
No!
不行！
You have to take chances in a relationship.
你要把握機會建立好關係
You have to be supportive.
你必須獲得支持
I don't need her to fit in. I just need her to be safe.
我不需要她加入，我要她安全
Just rent "Dirty Dancing", tell her you love her.
租片『熱舞十七』然後告訴她你愛她
It's important to enjoy life while you still can.
知道嗎，在活著時享受生活是很重要的
Victoria just accepted a contract from MI6 to kill all 3 of us.
維多利亞剛從MI6接了殺我們的任務
You don't think she'd do that, do you?
她不會這麼做，對嗎？
She's a friend.
她是我們的朋友
Are you stupid? You never took a contract out to kill a friend?
你笨蛋啊，你沒接過殺朋友的任務嗎？
She called to give us fair warning.
她告訴我們還警告我們
Come on. There's one more thing.
走吧，還有一件事
Han just went number one.
韓會第一個過來的
Why don't they just dip our balls in honey...
為什麼我們不把蛋蛋放入蜂蜜裏…
and stake us to an ant farm?
然後再扔到螞蟻窩裏呢？
Come on.
來吧
Whoa!
哇！
Crazy old bastard.
瘋狂的老混蛋
Frank, do you feel old?
法蘭克，你覺得老了嗎？
Not really.
沒什麼感覺
Me neither.
我也是
Crazy sometimes, I guess.
我想也許有時候很瘋狂
Who's Han?
誰是韓？
Korean. Counter intel.
一個韓國小子
Frank put him in jail for a few years.
法蘭克抓了他，害他坐好幾年牢
We should be super scared of him?
我們應該害怕他嗎？
Yes. He is the best contract killer in the world.
是的，他是世界最頂級的殺手
I've got a hit off an old alias, silent for almost 20 years.
我找到他們的舊名，已經20年沒用了
He's dodging watch lists.
進入查看頁面
Bingo. Private flight to Paris scheduled for 0900 out of Teterboro.
搞定了，九點坐私人飛機從泰特波羅飛往巴黎
Find their hotel. Get blueprints and workups on the day and night managers.
查明賓館，找出白天和晚間的值班經理
Have Vance meet us on the ground.
叫文森在著陸時見我們
泰特波羅,新澤西
They're 1 floor down. 2 adioining rooms.
他們在一樓，兩間套房
Surveillance is almost up and running.
到處都佈置監視器
This is going to be easier than I thought.
比我想像容易多了
Hello. Speaking.
你好，請說
Yes.
是的
Where are they?
他們在哪裏？
They were here. They ordered room service at 1 o'clock.
他們來過，一點時還叫了客房服務
What do you mean "The plane is prepped"?
你說『飛機離開』是什麼意思？
I think someone stole your plane.
我想有人偷了你的飛機
I'm really going to enioy killing him.
我真的要把他殺了
Get me a gun that really hurts.
給我一支火力最大的槍
How good is this guy?
這傢伙實力如何？
Han is the best contract killer in the world.
韓是世界頂級的殺手
Frank is in some vey deep dog doo.
法蘭克應該是十分幸運了
He's not gonna kill me.
他不會殺我的
Yeah. Nobody kills Frank Moses.
是啊，沒有人殺得了法蘭克·摩西
Right!
沒錯！
The people he really doesn't like, he tortures for a long time first.
他實在不討人喜歡，他虐待他一陣子
Can we just focus on tying to catch The Frog?
我們能不能集中精神來抓青蛙呢？
What's the action plan for target acquisition and rendition?
捉捕和運輸的計劃行動是什麼	？
Marvin?
馬文？
Quit teaching her stuff!
別教她一些亂七八糟的！
Nice.
真棒
What do you think the most expensive bottle of wine in the world costs?
你覺得世界上最貴的酒怎麼樣？
Chateau d'Yquem 1847.
伊甘酒莊，1847年的
Maybe 5, 6 bottles left in the world. It's pretty pricey.
世界上也許只有五六瓶，非常稀有
Maybe we should get a bottle and Try to catch The Frog with it.
或許我應該弄一瓶來抓青蛙
巴黎
My God, this is so romantic!
天啊，真是浪漫！
Come here. Keep your head down.
來吧，低著頭
But we have to go to the le Saint Louis for gelato.
但我們必須去聖路易吃冰淇淋
I don't think so.
我不這麼認為
Really? What about the...
是嗎？那麼…
Frank, is that?
法蘭克，這是？
Hello, Frank.
你好，法蘭克
Have you seen her since?
你以前見過他嗎？
Nope.
沒有
God, I've missed you.
天啊，我好想念你啊
Who is she?
她是誰？
Trouble.
冤家
How are things?
最近如何？
Yeah, Frank, how are things?
啊，法蘭克，最近如何？
Sarah...
莎拉…
This is Katia.
這位是卡嘉
Yeah. Hi.
你好
I need to speak with you. Immediately.
我有話要跟你說，現在
What the hell was that?
到底是怎麼回事？
Katja Petrokovich. Russian Counter Intelligence.
卡嘉，反俄羅斯組織人員
I think we should hear what she has to say.
我想我們應該聽聽她要說什麼
Frank...
法蘭克…
You don't know the half of it.
你不瞭解的
She and Frank were young.
她在法蘭克年輕時
He didn't have the slightest idea she was working for the Russians.
他還不知道她為俄羅斯工作
She's Frank Moses' kyptonite.
她是法蘭克·摩西的剋星
I like you with no hair.
我喜歡你頭光禿禿的
Bald men are so sey. Virile.
光頭男比較性感
Wow.
哇
She's cute. Where did you find her? Nebraska?
她很漂亮，你在哪裏撿的？內布拉斯加嗎？
Kansas.
堪薩斯
So what was it you wanted to talk to me about?
那麼你想告訴我什麼呢？
I would like to believe that the US didn't plant...
我還是相信美國沒有計劃…
a weapon of mass destruction in Moscow. But I don't.
在莫斯科設置大規模殺傷武器，但我不這麼認為
Why are you in Paris?
你來巴黎做什麼？
We come evey fall for Strike Season and for the weather.
我們每年秋天都來，因為天氣不錯
The US seems to think you're nuclear terrorists.
美國似乎認為你是恐怖份子
Russia wants complete access.
俄羅斯方面想掌控全局
You agree now or I'll hand you over to the US government.
現在你要同意，或者把你交給美國政府
Can't we just kill her?
我們能直接殺了她嗎？
Excuse me for one second.
不好意思
Can I talk to you?
我們能談談嗎？
What? Uh huh. Sure thing.
什麼？哦，當然
I was shocked.
我很震驚
I know. She was kinda counting your teeth with her tongue.
我知道，她把你的牙齒舔得很乾淨
A little, yeah.
是啊，有點
Can she go now?
她現在能走了嗎？
We don't really have a choice. We need her to help us.
我們別無選擇，我們需要她的幫忙
I promise there is nothing between us.
我發誓，我們之間沒什麼
No, sir. This guy's not giving us anything.
長官，這裏什麼都沒有
Website's been scrubbed.
網站已經被移除了
NSA intercepted a dispatch to the Kremlin from Paris.
NSA攔截到了，從克里姆林宮發到巴黎的信號
Moses is going after someone called "The Frog".
摩西在找叫『青蛙』的人
The Frog.
『青蛙』
So they call him "The Frog" because he's French?
他們叫他『青蛙』難道他是法國人
No. He poisoned the water supply at KGB headquarters...
不，他在KGB總部的供水系統下毒…
with the Amazon tree frog poison.
用亞馬遜的毒青蛙
He must have been wiping those little tree humpers for years.
他一定收集了這些小東西好幾年
Incapacitated 1600 people and left with evey secret we had.
毒死了600人，帶走了我們的機密
The guy makes a fortune selling information.
這傢伙有賣情報的運氣
He knows so much even the US won't touch him.
他知道美國方面不會碰他
The hard part is gonna be taking him alive.
最難的是無法活捉他
Superb.
很好
Wine is wine.
酒歸酒
I want to buyAmerican air defense protocols.
我要買美國防禦協議
Why is it terrorists never appreciate Burgundy?
為什麼恐怖份子不懂欣賞葡萄酒？
I don't think you know who you're dealing with.
我可不認為你懂得怎麼處理
競標價格
出售
Confirmed. It's him. It's the Frog.
確定是他，是青蛙
Just don't look at him, right?
記住別看著他的眼睛，好嗎？
Just act natural.
自然一點
And don't look him right in the eyes.
不管怎樣，別看著他的眼睛
Check.
收到
Remember, don't look right at him.
記住，別看著他
Marvin, you All right?
馬文，你沒事吧？
Yeah.
好
Get her outta here.
把她帶離開這裏
When?
何時？
Now!
現在！
Get a car!
弄輛車子！
Is that?
是那個嗎？
Cut them off!
攔住他們！
This is not a good idea!
這不是個好主意！
She's not gonna get there first!
她不會是第一個先到的！
Sidewalk!
走人行道！
Watch the curb!
小心路邊！
Yes!
很好！
Happy trails, bozo!
追上他，笨蛋！
Don't you think we should let...
你不認為我們應該…
Shut your pie hole, Marvin!
閉上你的嘴，馬文！
Don't you think we should let...
你不認為我們應該讓…
Hush!
安靜！
Incoming!
來了！
Bastard! Sidewalk!
混蛋！人行道！
What the?
這是什麼？
She's fine.
她沒事的
Got him.
追上他
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Got him.
捉到他了
Look! What is she doing?
她在幹什麼？
I'm begging.
我在乞討
Yeah, yeah. I got this.
是啊，我得到了
I so got this.
我得到了
I hate her so much.
我非常討厭她
You're wasting your time!
你是在浪費時間！
You're going to regret this more than you can possibly imagine.
你將無法想像你會有多後悔
You know who we are?
你知道我們是誰嗎？
Yes, of course.
是啊，當然
Tell us about Nightshade.
告訴我們有關『暗影行動』
You think I'm going to roll over for you hegemonic...
你認為我會屈服你的暴行嗎…
Mickey Mouse loving Americans?
米奇老鼠熱愛美國嗎？
Leave Mickey out of it.
別提米奇老鼠了
1947 P trus?
1947年，P，trus的？
Yes. That one's rather...
是的，那個很…
God's sake!
天啊！
Wait wait wait! That bottle!
等等，那一瓶！
How do we find it?
我們要怎麼找到？
Never!
永遠找不到！
Nightshade was the plot of lunatics.
『暗影行動』是個瘋狂的計劃
I used to be like you.
我曾經像你一樣
Driven by ideology and fear...
受意識和恐懼的驅動…
with no love of what's beautiful in the world.
對這美麗的世界沒有愛
I can't trust animals like you!
我不能相信像你這樣的畜生！
Do what you will.
隨你怎麼做
Death is easy.
死亡很簡單
It's not about the destination.it's about the journey.
但這不是目的，主要是過程
Death is an art form in Russia.
死亡在俄國是一門藝術
There are so many ways to take a man to bits.
有很多方法讓一個人開口
Shall we start with a Chechen facelift? Hold him down!
我們從剝下他的臉皮開始，壓住他！
Stop! Stop it!
不要！住手！
This is how we do it.
這就是我們的風格
Please. You're so brave.
求求你，你這麼勇敢
But you have to understand...
但是你必須明白…
we're doing this for the right reasons. And this...
我們這麼做有正當的理由，還有…
This isn't worth your life.
這不值得你去賣命
You must have something to live for.
你一定有活下來的目標
Art.
藝術
Wine.
美酒
Women?
女人？
Hey.
嘿
Help us.
救救我們
We need this information.
我們需要這份情報
You'll be helping us save the world. Please.
你會幫助我們救救這個世界，求求你
You, I'll help.
你，我會幫助的
Excuse me.
抱歉
Thank you.
謝謝你
And you can suck it.
你去死吧
Baby? Honey?
寶貝？親愛的？
Seriously? You hooked up with that?
真的嗎？你這樣勾搭上的？
What a woman.
女人啊
Is that the same dress?
那是同樣一件嗎？
They look the same to you?
你看起來是一樣的嗎？
No one ever called me Frank Moses' kyptonite.
沒有人稱我是『法蘭克·摩西的剋星』
Frank's crazy about you.
法蘭克對你太著迷了
I've never seen him afraid of anything except losing you.
我從沒看過他那麼害怕失去了你
What if I'm ruining his life?
如果我毀了他的人生怎麼辦？
Frank is a vey simple creature with vey simple needs.
法蘭克是個單純生物，他的需求很簡單
It's killing...
就是殺戮…
eating...
進食…
sexing...
做愛…
eating...
進食…
Killing, I guess.
殺戮，我猜是吧
What's your point?
什麼意思呢？
I can't believe you kissed The Frog.
我無法相信你吻了這只『青蛙』
Well, I've kissed a lot of frogs.
我可親吻過很多『青蛙』呢
I got something for ya.
我有東西給你
What is it?
是什麼？
The key to The Frog's security deposit box.
『青蛙』秘密保險櫃的鑰匙
From?
在哪裏？
Credit Lyonnais.
里昂信貸銀行
Baby, I have a request.
寶貝，我有個請求
How would you feel about going out to dinner with me tonight?
今晚與我一起出去吃晚餐如何？
It is Paris, after all.
畢竟這裏是巴黎
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
是啊，好啊！
Stay here. I'll be right back.
待在這裏，我馬上回來
I need you, Frank.
我需要你，法蘭克
It's not a good time.
這可不是好時機
One of our old assets has some real information.
我們有個老同事說有重要的情報
He needs to meet with us right now.
他需要馬上見我們
Nah.
不行
Frank, what are you doing? She's kyptonite.
法蘭克，你在幹什麼，她是你的剋星
I'll handle it.
我會處理好的
Are you sure?
你肯定嗎？
Yeah.
是
It's not okay. It's just some work. No, it's not fun.
不太好吧，還有工作呢，不是開玩笑的
Go. You and Svetlana work it out.
走，去和斯維特蘭娜幹活吧
I promise you that I will be back in time for dinner.
我保證會回來一起吃晚餐的
I'll be back.
我會回來的
Keep her safe.
照顧她的安全
What happened to us, Frank?
我們怎麼了，法蘭克？
Well...
嗯…
You betrayed me. You set me up. Tried to kill me.
你背叛我，你坑了我，你打算殺了我
I tried to kill you.
我是打算殺了你
They were good times, weren't they?
這是最好的機會，不是嗎？
If you'd asked me to betray my county, you know I would have.
知道嗎，如果你要我背叛我的國家，你知道我會的
Yes, madam.
是的，夫人
My God.
天啊
You know, I looked you up once.
知道嗎，我見過你們
You were in a bungalow in Los Angeles.
在洛杉磯的屋子裏
There were roses out in front.
屋前滿滿的玫瑰
But I lost my nerve.
但我失去了我的自信
So what do you want?
那麼你想怎樣呢？
It was all about work with you. Rules.
和你都只是工作關係，規則
Not rules.
不是規則
Right and wrong.
是對與錯
It's harder for me not to follow orders.
違抗命令對我來說很難
Despite my personal feelings.
我可以不顧個人感受
But feelings don't matter any more than right or wrong.
但感覺與對錯無關
Orders matter.
命令至關重要
Orders?
命令？
Russia will handle things from here.
俄國會操縱這裏的一切
I'm taking the key.
我要拿走鑰匙
I can't let that happen.
我不會讓這種事發生的
No?
不會嗎？
I can't feel my arms.
我的胳臂失去知覺了
Enioy Kansas.
享受堪薩斯吧
He's out.
他失去知覺了
He might be awake.
或許會清醒過來
Good. So he can feel it.
很好，那就會有感覺了
Did you ever, ever in your entire career...
在你整個生涯中…
let yourself get drugged?
有沒有什麼讓你變得麻木？
I just don't like her!
我就是不喜歡她！
And now she has the key!
現在她有鑰匙了！
She doesn't have the key. She has a key.
她沒有鑰匙，她有鑰匙
What?
什麼？
I knew she would play him like a banjo at an Ozark hoedown.
我知道她會讓他中計
So I have the key.
所以我保留鑰匙了
Water.
水
How long was I out for?
我還要多久才能離開？
Some of it's his.
有一些是他的
Et tu, Marvin?
馬文？
Style is the only constant in life.
風格是生活中唯一不變的
We didn't come to Paris on vacation.
我們來巴黎不是渡假的
Shopping's what I thought you did in Paris...
我以為你是來巴黎『血拼』的…
with your boyriend's money...
用你男朋友的錢…
while you're waiting for him...
當你在等他的時候…
to wake up from being taken down...
在沉迷中醒過來…
by his skanky, slutty, Russian bitch ex girlfriend.
他的前任俄國女婊子
So thanks.
非常感謝
Thanks for the compliment for the fur.
感謝你所有的恭維
For telling me that I look nice in my dress.
告訴我我穿這條裙子很好看
It makes me feel really good.
讓我感覺真的很好
And it makes me feel very loving towards you also.
也讓我感覺你也很好
Why is she doing this to me?
為什麼他對我這麼做
We can get a taxi over here.
我們可以叫計程車
Listen, I gotta tell you something.
聽著，我有些事要跟你說
You have to share your feelings to evolve your relationship.
你需要把你的感受告訴周圍的人
Even if it seems uncomfortable at first.
雖然剛開始很彆扭
Say you're pinned down in a firefight.
譬如你被困在火海裏
If you stay where you are, you're gonna die. Okay?
如果你待在原地就會燒死，知道嗎？
So what do you do?
那麼，你怎麼做？
Make the run.
逃跑啊
Yes. You have got to make the run...
對，你必須跑…
to emotional safety.
跑到安全的地方
You dead yet, Moses?
你死了嗎，摩西？
Not yet.
還沒
Where's my plane?!
我的飛機在哪裏？！
In my ass!
在我屁股裏！
It's in an airport outside of Paris.
在巴黎郊區的機場
What are you? Shut up!
你在說什麼？閉嘴！
Let's get outta here.
離開這裏
Marvin?
馬文？
Yeah?
是？
Is that a stick of dynamite in your pocket?
你袋子裏的炸彈做什麼用的？
Yeah, but I'm saving it for an emergency.
是用在緊急情況下的
This is kind of an emergency, isn't it?
這就是緊急情況，對嗎？
里昂信貸銀行
巴黎
The key I gave her is connected to...
我給他的鑰匙是用來…
a particularly nasty terrorist cell and their safe deposit box.
開啟保險櫃的，恐怖份子都很想要
The French take this kinda thing pretty seriously.
法國人正在緊急通緝她
That's enough.
夠了
Put me down now! Now!
把我放下！快點！
All right.
好吧
We gotta move quickly, Moscow will have her out within the hour.
我們的快點行動，莫斯科一小時內就會把她弄出來
For the love of Mike.
為了邁克的愛
All right.
好吧
I'm still not talking to you.
我沒有跟你說話
This is an MI6 report on Project Nightshade.
這是MI6關於『暗影行動』的報告
It's about the operative that placed the device.
關於行動裝置的地點
They took him into custody and put him on ICE.
他們把他暫時關到ICE
What's ICE?
什麼是ICE？
Incarcerate, Cannot Execute.
抓進去就無法逃離了
Who would they keep on ICE for 32 years?
他們會把誰關在ICE待32年？
Come on. Gotta go.
來吧，該走了
英格蘭
How could she have possibly found us?
她怎麼可能發現我們呢？
'Cause I called her and told her we were coming.
因為我告訴她，我們要來了
I couldn't take the pressure of not knowing.
我無法承受事情不確定的壓力
Why isn't she shooting at us?
為什麼她不朝我們開槍？
That should buy us 24 hours.
那會給我們多24小時時間
Hello, sweetie.
哈羅，親愛的
The nex time you 2 make a plan like this, at least let me in on it.
下次你要幹這種事，先告訴我一聲
You're compromising me.
你們要犧牲我
Who knows what some girl is gonna squeeze out of you?
誰知道那些女孩要供出你？
Where'd you get the bodies?
你從哪裏弄到這些屍體的？
My freezer.
我的冷凍庫
Come on. Wake up.
來吧，醒醒
Yeah? What the hell's going on?
到底怎麼回事？
Sir?
長官？
Get anything from The Frog?
從『青蛙』那裏得到什麼情報？
No, he took some sorta poison before we really talked.
沒有，他在我們詢問前服了一種毒藥
I don't think he's gonna say anything now.
我認為他現在什麼也不會說
You've got to find Moses and Boggs.
你必須去找摩西和博格斯
Don't wory. I'm on the trail.
別擔心，我正在路上
倫敦
On your right, you see the famous Tower of London.
在右邊，你看到的是出名的倫敦塔
And shortly, we'll be passing under the Tower Bridge.
我們會穿過塔底下
It's a fortress.
一個堡壘
It's an asylum for the criminally insane.
它是秘密關押罪犯的監獄
He's in the ICE unit.
他在ICE裏面
That's an MI6 Alpha Level secure facility...
那是MI6，A級安保地點…
buried deep within that building.
深藏在那座大樓中
It's like a prison within a prison.
就像監獄中的監獄
How are we gonna get in there?
我們要怎麼進去？
She wants my head!
他想要我的頭！
It's a Papist plot.
這是天主教的陰謀
It's that bitch May Queen of Scots. She wants my head.
那個蘇格蘭賤人皇后，他想要我的頭
What are you doing? No!
你在幹什麼？不！
Get me Cecil. I'm the Queen of England!
給我叫塞西爾，我才是蘇格蘭皇后！
Don't take me to the Tower!
不要帶我去城堡！
I'll have your head for this, you bitch!
我會砍下你的頭的，婊子！
No! No!
不！不！
"Uneasy lies the head that wears the crown."
頭戴王冠可不簡單啊
They're plotting against me. All of them.
他們所有的人都想要反抗我
There's a good queen.
這才是個好皇后
Stuff it, you old bat.
別說了，老妖怪
Thank you.
謝了
Not so much the "old", if you don't mind.
如果不介意，別再叫我老妖怪了
I think it was really good.
我覺得這個很不錯
I thought I was channeling Bette Davis.
我以為在引導Bette，Davis呢
Good morning. Dr. Jones to see prisoner number 17, please.
早安，瓊斯醫生想要看一下17號患者
Dr. Jones? Are you with MI6?
瓊斯醫生，來自MI6的嗎？
Certainly, not anymore.
當然，但不再是了
I don't seem to have you on my list.
電腦表單上沒有你的名字
Bloody thing's not working. Why's that?
這東西不好使用，為什麼？
You're supposed to use...
你應該使用…
Lay down on the ground.
趴在地板上，很好
Number 121. There it is.
121病房，就是那裏
Frank!
法蘭克！
Who are you? You're visitors? Who are you looking for?
你們是誰？參觀的嗎？找誰呢？
We love having visitors, don't we, fellas?
我們喜歡參觀者，不是嗎，夥伴們？
Dr. Bailey?
貝利教授？
Doctor Bailey?
Yes. Who did you expect to find here?
是啊，不然還會有誰呢？
Sir...
教授…
What?
怎麼？
I saw you die.
我看到你死了
Saw me die? Who is he?
看到我死了？他是誰？
Frank?
法蘭克？
Frank Moses, my dear fellow! How are you, old sport?
法蘭克·摩西，我親愛的朋友！你好嗎？
So glad to see you. So glad you came by.
很高興見到你，歡迎你來
We've been expecting you. Haven't we, fellas?
我們期待很久了，不是嗎？
My God, why are you so old?
天啊，你怎麼這麼老了？
Good lord!
老天啊！
Sir...
教授…
What?
什麼？
You've been locked up here for 32 years.
你已經被關32年了
Frankie, you've gotta be kidding me. Come on, put 'em up.
來吧，法蘭克，開什麼玩笑，玩一下
32 years. How exraordinay. Who are you?
32年，怎麼可能，你叫什麼名字？
Victoria.
維多利亞
Victoria! You should read this. Lenin. " State and Revolution."
維多利亞，你應該看看這個，列寧的《國家與革命》
Jolly good time. Stalin got it wrong, of course.
快樂的時光，斯大林肯定會搞砸的
Where are we going, Frank? Are you taking us to the opera?
我們要去哪裏呢，法蘭克？歌劇院嗎？
Is that where we're going? We love the opera, don't we, fellas?
我們要去哪裏？我們都喜歡歌劇，不是嗎？
The opera and the champagne and the strawberries all round.
有香檳和草莓的歌劇院
sorry, my dear, what is your name again?
抱歉，親愛的，再請問你的名字？
Victoria.
維多利亞
sorry, it's the drugs they're feeding me, it's my short term memory.
抱歉，這是藥物作用，影響我的記憶
Something that's meant to keep us peaceful or harmless!
一種讓我平靜而又無害的東西！
Anmay, it's around here somewhere, but I don't know where.
反正就在附近，但我又不知道在哪裏
Dr. Bailey, we need your help.
貝利教授，我們需要你的幫助
Do you remember Nightshade?
你記得『暗影行動』嗎？
I'm looking for my pipe and my St. Christopher medallion.
抱歉，我在找煙斗和聖克裏斯托弗獎章
Boys gave it to someone. They were little boys.
那些年輕人把它給別人了，都是些小孩
And now it's gone somehow.
大概跑到哪裏去了
Oh shit!
喔，糟糕！
Hey, Frankie, I'm over here.
法蘭克，我在這裏
I found it. It was in my pocket the whole time.
我找到了，一直在我的口袋裏
I couldn't find my damn pipe, though. But here it is.
儘管我找不到煙斗了，還好在這裏
sorry, my dear, what was the question you asked me?
抱歉，親愛的，你剛才問我什麼？
Do you remember Nightshade?
你記得『暗影行動』嗎？
Vaguely. It was some kind of a bomb, I believe.
我記得那是一種炸彈
People are looking for that weapon. People who want to use it.
有人正在找它，想要使用它
Oh dear. Yes, I do understand of course. Believe me.
親愛的，我瞭解，相信我
But I made many things for the Americans and...
我為美國製造了很多東西…
Nightshade turned out to be a bit of a nightmare.
『暗影行動』是最嚇人的傑作
It was quite different. Turned out to be too dangerous.
與眾不同，又非常危險
So naturally, they had to lock me up in this place.
所以他們自然要把我關在這裏
And after what they did to me, I think it's perfectly natural...
即使他們對我做了這些事後，我覺得這很正常…
I tell them all to go F off!
我警告過他們要滾遠點！
MI6 tried to fake Bailey's death?
MI6想製造貝利死亡的謊言？
Why? What are they hiding?
為什麼？他們想隱瞞什麼？
You're gonna have to go. You're gonna have to go find out.
你得走了，他們發現你了
You know they're gonna Ty and kill me.
他們想殺了我的
I'll call you from Russia.
到俄國再找你
Maintenance to Bridge 7.
維護7號橋
We got a breach in Maximum Security.
安全系統出現緊急狀況
Secure!
保全！
What's so important?
什麼事那麼重要？
I just heard from my source at MI6 that Edward Bailey's alive and on the run.
我剛從MI6得到消息，愛德華貝利還活著，並已經逃走了
That's not possible.
這不可能
This is bigger than a rogue General and his unexploded ordinance.
這比想像中的麻煩還大
What don't I know?
我還有什麼不知道的？
The game has changed.
遊戲改變了
The things Bailey knows are too dangerous.
貝利知道的事情太危險了
If Bailey or Nightshade fall into terrorist hands, millions will die.
如果貝利或者暗影行動落入恐怖份子，將有數萬人會喪生
Holy shit, it's real.
喔，天啊，這是真的
Unless we secure it, that weapon's going off in the middle of Moscow.
除非我們銷毀它，那個武器正在莫斯科中心地區
Right now, that's our best case scenario.
這就是我們最好的應急措施
俄羅斯
多羅霍沃空軍基地
Guys?
夥計們？
Welcome, my friends.
歡迎，我的朋友們
So, it is true. You're alive.
傳言是真的，你還活著
Tell me, then, where is this device?
告訴我，是誰操控的？
Who?
誰？
Work in progress.
我們在努力
I never thought I'd be smuggling...
我從來沒有想過…
Frank Moses into the heart of Mother Russia.
帶法蘭克·摩西到俄羅斯中心地區去
Me, neither.
我也是
Before I forget. A little something.
在我忘記前，這裏有點小東西
If you are caught or Han catches you...
如果你被抓了或韓抓了你…
suicide pill is a much better option than what you face.
服藥自殺是最好的選擇
You die with Russian smile on.
就算死，也會死得很漂亮
Good luck.
祝好運
Mr. Bailey.
貝利教授
Yes, Frank?
法蘭克？
Is there any way you could tell us where you hid the nuclear weapon?
有什麼方式可以告訴我們核武器在哪裏？
Look at all those cows. They're beautiful.
這些堡壘，可真是漂亮啊
Yeah.
堡壘
Cows?
母牛？
Hi! Yoo hoo!
嗨！
That's not good.
情況不妙
莫斯科
We have eyes on, Frank.
我們被跟蹤了，法蘭克
Where's my plane?
我的飛機在哪裏？
They paid me to kill you.
他們雇我來殺你
They didn't say I had to do it all at once.
沒有說要保留全屍
別動！
把手放頭上
波士奇呼叫，這裏有警察受傷
我們需要醫生
別動，把手放頭上
What's wrong with him?
他怎麼了？
Wow.
哇
What is this place?
這是什麼地方？
My first safe house.
我第一個安全屋
Untouched, since 1984.
鄰家女孩，是從1984年開始的
Fugu poison?
河豚毒？
Fugu poison is deadly stuff. Terrible death.
那可是劇毒
This little gizmo? XKG gas. I invented it.
看到了嗎？XKG毒氣，我發明的
We tried to take out old Fidel Castro in '61 in Cuba.
我們想在61年刺殺古巴總統卡斯楚
That didn't work though.
但是沒有奏效
Any tea, Frank?
選一個吧，法蘭克？
Why does Han hate you so much?
為什麼韓那麼討厭你？
Not enough hugs as a child.
從小時候起他就討厭我
Frank framed him for stealing state secrets.
法蘭克盜取了國家的機密
So he went from being a highly decorated counter intel officer...
然後從一個優秀情報員…
to being a pariah.
變成可怕的殺手
What's ironic is that Frank...
最諷刺的是，法蘭克…
actually created the circumstances for his own death.
總在刺殺時出現了些狀況
It's poetic.
很戲劇性
I ain't dead yet.
我還沒有死
Should you eat that?
你在吃那東西？
Is that safe?
安全嗎？
It's before they had that, you know, "sell by" date stuff.
它還是在，過期之前
Did you get to meet Castro?
所以你見過卡斯楚了？
Who?
誰？
Did you get to meet Castro?
你見過卡斯楚了？
Yes, I did. About 2 weeks after Kennedy was assassinated.
當然，在甘迺迪死後的二星期
Talking of which, Frank...
順便說一下，法蘭克…
I'm starting to remember more and more who I am...
我開始記起來我是誰了…
and who I was and the weapons I made.
我以前幹什麼的，還有我製造的武器
My God, it really is amazing.
天啊，太神奇了
How efficiently those boys from MI6, God bless 'em...
MI6的人都是好人，上帝保佑他們…
But they really do throw us away. Don't they, old sport?
但他們確實遺棄了我們，不是嗎，老兄？
When we're no longer convenient, I suppose.
我們年齡大了，大概吧
As though we'd never given them the best years of our lives.
好像我們沒有把最好的時光獻給它
Bit of a ioke, really.
真是個天大的笑話
Yes, vey strange.
沒錯，真奇怪
Do you remember where Nightshade is?
你記得『暗影行動』在哪裏嗎？
I'm sorry, my dear?
抱歉，親愛的？
Do you remember where Nightshade is?
你記得『暗影行動』在哪裏嗎？
Oh, yes.
當然記得
This feels right.
好像是穿過這裏
It's around here somewhere. I'm sure this time.
我來過這裏，我肯定
Eveything looks different completely.
一切都變不一樣了
Maybe it's over here.
可能是穿過這裏
It's been hours.
一小時了
Yeah, this is it.
就是這裏
Here we are.
我們到了
How are those Jimmy Choos working out for you?
你覺得這事和吉米周有什麼關係？
The entrance is up there.
入口在上面
約翰爸爸
Who's Papa John?
誰是約翰爸爸？
It's new.
剛聽到的
Entrance to what?
去哪裏的入口？
Secret tunnels through the old catacombs.
穿過古陵寢的秘密通道
Brezhnev used it to sneak his mistress in.
這曾是布裏滋涅夫情婦的秘密通道
In where?
在那裏嗎？
In there.
在那裏
The Kremlin?
克里姆林宮？
The weapon is in the Kremlin?
核彈在克里姆林宮？
It's the one place they wouldn't look.
那是他們唯一不會檢查的地方
Jesus.Do you mind keeping it warm?
天啊，你能讓它保暖嗎？
You have no idea the damage you've done.
你不知道你所做造成了多大破壞
You kept one of our own locked up for 32 years.
你居然把自己人關了32年
I have kept the world safe.
我要讓世界維持和平
If that weapon falls into the wrong hands.
如果核武落入不法份子手中呢
The weapon?
武器？
You haven't the slightest idea.
你真是什麼都不懂
You must let me call Moses. He doesn't know what he's walking into.
你要馬上聯繫摩西，他不知道是陷阱
You've had your chance. It's over.
你已經有過這機會的，都結束了
I'm sorry, Victoria.
我很抱歉，維多利亞
sorry, my ass.
去你媽的抱歉
They say you're a legend around here.
他們說你是這裏的傳奇
I've...
但是，我…
I've never heard of you.
我從沒有聽說過
Must have been a bit before my time.
一定要說些我以前的事
You've heard of me now.
現在聽說過我了吧
How is it possible they never picked up the radiation signature from that bomb?
他們怎麼檢測不到核彈的幅射呢？
That's the million dollar question.
這個問題很好
Hey, gang. This is new.
嘿，夥計，這是新的
What do you think is behind that wall?
牆的後面是什麼呢？
I think Russians.
應該是俄國人
If anybody sees that hole, we're dead.
要是有人發現這個洞，我們就死定了
I'm gonna need you to help me to disarm the weapon.
我需要你解除核武裝置
Somebody's gotta guard the door.
要有人在外面把風
No.
不
But...
但是…
You'll need this.
你需要這個
主席
這是20分鐘前被帶進紅場的
檢查建築物，軍隊戒備！
One more time.
再來一次，是的
Great. What does that mean?
很好，是什麼意思？
"Gas leak. Maintenance is coming."
瓦斯外洩，工作人員很快就會來了
Good. And then they'll move on.
很好，然後他們就會走
What if they don't?
如果不走呢？
Want a gun?
想要支槍嗎？
Yes.
好啊
No gun.
不能拿槍
Just don't move.
別動
You're a security guard.
你是安全警衛
Don't smile. You can't smile.
別笑，你不能笑
You never leave your post. Okay?
只要不離開崗位就行了，好嗎？
Nice.
很好
2 shots, here and here.
兩個攝影頭，這裏和這裏
Drag the body in there and repeat as necessay.
把他拖進去，來一個殺一個
No safety.
不安全嗎
不安全
Frank, I don't like the Kremlin so much.
法蘭克，我真不喜歡克里姆林宮
And I like being underneath it even less.
不過我喜歡在底下
Here we are.
到了
That's great. It's just like yesterday.
太好了，沒什麼變化
There's my crow bar. Look at this.
這是我的舊鐵撬，你們看
There.
這裏
Hey, look, chaps.
大家來看
That's my old pipe. I knew I'd left it somewhere...
我的舊煙斗，我記得放在…
My dear wife bought this for me in 1969. It was our wedding anniversay.
我妻子1969年給我的結婚禮物
Oh yes!
喔，對了！
This is Nightshade, by the way.
這個是『暗影行動』
There.
這裏
Is that...?
那是什麼…？
That's Red Mercuy.
紅色水銀柱
Red Mercuy?
紅色水銀柱？
We were always told it was a Cold War myth.
我們冷戰就是為了這個在拚命
Yes, they said it couldn't be done, but I did it.
是，他們說製造不出來，但我做到了
If that's Red Mercuy...
如果這是真的紅色水銀柱…
you can zip it up in a backpack and take it on the White House tour.
我們就可以用背包帶著走
It's undetectable.
然後在不被發現的狀況毀掉白宮
No signature. No fallout.
沒有幅射，沒有預兆
This weapon will entirely change the balance of international power...
這是種需要能量平衡的武器…
overnight. Just like that.
就像…
We're all gonna die.
我們都會死的
On your knees.
跪下
Katia.
卡嘉
No government should have this weapon.
任何政府都不該擁有這武器
Not yours. And not mine.
你們不能，我們也不能
I have orders.
我有命令
This isn't about orders. This is about right and wrong.
這不是命令的事，是有關對與錯的事
Don't.
別過來
Did you really come to see me in the States?
你真的到美國來看我嗎？
Yes.
是的
What color were the flowers outside my house?
我屋子外的花是什麼顏色？
Yellow.
黃色
我注意到你一直背靠著牆
瓦斯外洩，工作人員很快就會來了
我叫帕夏，晚點去喝一杯吧？
什麼？
我想你也注意到我了！
What in the name of? Hey!
這是在幹什麼！
What are you doing kissing this guy?
你為什麼吻這個傢伙？
I didn't wanna kill him.
我不想殺他啊
What kinda stupid logic is that?
這是什麼狗屁邏輯？
What in the Sam Hill is she doing here?
她在這裏做什麼？
She's working with us again.
她跟我們一起工作
Like heck she is.
就她嗎
Why were you kissing that guy?
為什麼吻那個傢伙？
Kids, what happens in the Kremlin stays in the Kremlin.
孩子，不管發生什麼事，你們都要留在克里姆林宮裏
You are gonna have to explain this to me.
你要對我解釋一下
Hey, Comrades!
乾杯！
Here's to more success.
為我們的成功
Success.
成功
And saving the world!
拯救世界！
Saving the world!
拯救全世界！
I got this. Right back.
我要接個電話，等一下回來
Hey.
嘿
Where are you?
你在哪裏？
Moscow.
莫斯科
He's a nutter, Francis.
他不是瘋子，法蘭克
MI6 didn't lock him up because he created the weapon...
MI6關他不是因為他製造武器…
but because he wants to see it go off.
因為他想要造反
Hello, Frank.
哈羅，法蘭克
That was Victoria, wasn't it?
是維多利亞，對嗎？
Telling you that I was some sort of a monster...
說我是怪物之類的…
who once wanted to destroy the Soviet empire.
想要摧毀蘇維埃帝國
Yeah. Vey slowly.
是，慢慢地
That's it. Good boy.
這就對了
Good. In you go.
走前面
Marvin...
馬文…
Guns down.
放下武器
Weapons down. Vey slowly.
放下武器，慢慢轉身
You planted the thing on WikiLeaks.
你一開始就在計劃了，是吧
Yes, it was a cell phone taken from a guard.
對，這是從警衛那裏弄來的電話
I was just itching to get my revenge on MI6.
我恨不得就在MI6里面報仇
Frank, you were absolutely marvelous the way you found The Frog.
法蘭克，你能找到『青蛙』只能說你運氣好
No one else could have found him.
別人都找不到
Jack?
傑克？
sorry, Frank, I made a deal already with Mr. Gordon for Red Mercuy.
抱歉，法蘭克，看來我要啟動炸彈了
Well done, Bailey.
做得好，貝利
Thanks.
謝謝
Nice to see you again.
很高興又見面了
Pick up the guns.
把槍收起來
Your county appreciates your sacrifice.
你的國家感謝你的犧牲
But your time's up.
你的時辰到了
Let's go.
我們走
It's time, Bailey.
是時候了，貝利
Yes, it is time.
對，是時候了
Vey Interesting. Rogue American agents turned nuclear terrorists...
很有趣，兩名美國特工變成恐怖份子…
kill top Russian officer.
還殺了俄國官員
Not good.
這可不太好
So long, Frank. So long, Marvin.
再見，法蘭克，再見，馬文
Come on, boys, let's go.
來，跟我來
Easy.
放鬆
Please, let me take that from you.
讓我來開門
I thought we were doing the debriefing in London.
我以為會在倫敦聽到任務報告
We were.
是的
But since you're such a sick, twisted bastard, you're going to Colorado.
但你目前還不安全，我們要去科羅拉多
There's a secret facility there, about a mile underground...
那裏有個秘密基地，大約離地一英里…
where you will spend your remaining years...
你將留在那裏渡過你的餘生…
having evey bit of knowledge plucked from that giant head of yours.
包括你頭腦裏的一切知識
Really?
真的嗎？
Frankly, it will make your last 32 years...
有趣的是，接下來的32年…
seem like a vacation in the Caribbean.
就好像在加勒比海渡假一樣
Cuff him.
把他銬起來
I say.
知道了
Well, well.
好吧，好吧
Bet you didn't see that coming. Did you, old man?
我打賭你一定沒想到，是嗎，老頭？
I must say, I didn't. Jolly good.
我只能說我的確沒有想到，很好
After you.
你先請
Thank you.Good morning, gentlemen.
先生們，謝謝，早安
What did he say?
他說什麼？
Ready.
預備
Do something. Do something.
想想辦法，想想辦法
I love you.
我愛你
At least Han didn't get us first.
至少韓不會先殺死我們
Really? You're gonna bring that up right now?
真的嗎？你現在才說這些？
There is nothing more sey in the whole world...
世界上沒有比這更性感的了…
than a beautiful woman...
一個漂亮的女人…
with an incredible gun.
跟一件絕妙的武器
You're such a romantic.
你在故做浪漫
Watch your eyes.
小心眼睛
Close your eyes.
閉上眼睛
I love the way your toes curl right before you fire.
我喜歡看你開槍時腳趾頭的動作
Hopeless.
真是沒救了
Freeze.
別動
I don't think you ought to point that idiotic thing at me.
我想你不該用那愚蠢的東西對著我
You should really start thinking about your security protocol.
你應該好好想想自己的安全
What the hell is that?
這是什麼？
That my dear boy,
這我的最愛
is an antidote...to the most powerul nerve agent ever created. Look.
這是我製造過最強的神經毒劑，看吧
Hello, boys.
永別了，年輕人
Hello, Mr. Davis.
永別了，戴維先生
And you didn't see that coming. Did you, old sport?
你沒想到會這樣，對嗎，老兄？
I'm sure you wouldn't want to miss what's coming ne.
接下來的好戲你一定不願意錯過的
It's a little antidote. Jolly good.
這是一個小小的解藥，很好
That's right.
很好
Good. Thank you.
好，謝謝
Jolly good.
很好
Honestly, Frank, 2 days and you're in front of a firing squad?
說實話，法蘭克，你才來這裏兩天而已？
Yeah. But look...
是的，但是…
No excuses. You're better than this. It's pathetic.
別找藉口，你應該做更好的，真失望
An American militay transport made an emergency landing in London.
美國領導人飛去倫敦了
Eveyone aboard was found dead.
飛機上所有的人都死了
Bailey has taken refuge in the Iranian embassy.
貝利劫持伊朗大使館人員當人質
The Iranian embassy?
伊朗大使館？
We've gotta go there.
我們必須去那裏
All right. Get ready.
好，做好準備
I'm gonna make sure we're cleared for takeoff.
我看看能不能起飛
If the world is here in a week...
如果世界沒有毀滅的話…
I will meet you in the Turks and Caicos.
我會在土耳其的凱科斯群島見你
And we will spend all night...
我們會在那裏渡過每一個夜晚…
beneath the stars.
在星空下
I don't speak Korean!
我不會說韓語！
You having fun yet?
你玩夠了嗎？
I'll let you know when I start having fun.
告訴你，我玩得正高興呢
You betrayed me.
你背叛了我
I had no choice.
我身不由己
You'd have done the same thing, if you were me.
如果是你也會這樣做的
How much is the US paying you?
美國給了你多少錢？
20 million.
二千萬
Are you kidding me?
你在開玩笑嗎？
I asked for more.
我還想更多呢
What happened to you?
你怎麼回事了？
You used to be a good agent.
以前你是很優秀的特工
Stop! Wait a minute.
停下！等等
Listen, I need your help.
聽著，我需要你的幫助
I know there's a part of you that wants to do the right thing.
我知道你想做正義之事
There is a weapon that's gonna be detonated...
有顆炸彈就要爆炸…
Bullshit.
胡說八道
It's not bullshit.
我沒有胡說
There's a bomb headed for London right now.
一顆炸彈就要降落到倫敦
11 million people are gonna lose their lives if you don't help me.
如果不幫我，一千一百萬人就會喪命
All right.
好吧
Let's go.
我們走
This doesn't mean I'm not going to kill you later.
這不表示以後我不會殺你
I know.
我知道
I think the way to make a relationship work...
我認為讓你們維持關係的長久方法…
is that neither of you give up who you are.
你們都不能放棄真正的自己
Don't you agree, Marvin?
你同意嗎，馬文？
Exactly. Exactly what Marvin says.
就是這樣，就像馬文所說的
Falling in love is like jumping off a cliff.
愛情就像蹦極一樣
You just have to believe and let go.
你必須相信他，並由他去
My God!
天啊！
Are you okay?
還好嗎？
No, he's All right.
不要，他沒問題
He's with us.
他加入我們了
We talked it out.
我們談好了
Kill Bailey. Secure the weapon. How hard can it be?
殺死貝利，解除武器，這很困難嗎？
The exernal security is vey heary but...
當然外面有重兵把守，但是…
inside there are hardcore Revolutionary Guards.
裏面還有精英革命軍
They are serious fanatics.
他們都很狂熱
The whole thing depends on her.
整件事就靠她了
You do realize, if they catch you, they will kill you.
你要明白，如果被捉到就死定了
LONDON
倫敦
I know this won't be easy for you, but don't wory.
我知道對你來說不容易，但是別擔心
Okay?
好嗎？
I've been thinking about...
我一直在想…
you and me.
你和我
And I just...
還有，我…
I got you something.
我有東西給你
Wow.
哇
You like it?
喜歡嗎？
I love it.
我很喜歡
7 rounds.
彈夾7發
Okay.
好
Not yet. I'm not ready.
我還沒準備好
Stop, no.
停住，不
Not right now. Wait.
不是現在，再等一下
If you don't do it, you're gonna blow it. Look at me.
如果錯過，你會毀了一切的
I'm gonna count to 3. In English.
我用英語數到三
Not now. No. Wait.
不是現在，等等
2...
2…
God damn it.
天啊
Hi.
嗨
She's gonna get killed.
她會被殺的
It's tough when they leave the nest.
他們離開巢穴時很難有機會
Frank, come on. A little trust.
法蘭克，拜託，相信我
She has talents you and I will never have.
她擁有你我都沒有的天賦
What talents?
什麼天賦？
People like her.
人們都喜歡她
If she lives, this'll be good for your relationship.
如果她活下來，對你們的關係很有幫助
You're right.
你是對的
And if there's one thing I know, it's women and covert ops.
我所知道的，女人與特工
That's 2 things.
這是兩件事
No, grasshopper.
不，小蚱蜢
It is not.
這不是
I wanna tell you a secret, Mr. Minister.
我要告訴你一個秘密，部長先生
Is she gonna make out with this guy, too?
她也要和那傢伙親熱了嗎？
What the hell was that?
這是什麼玩意？
Blomish poison.
毒藥
Paralysis and shooting pains will grip your entire body.
你全身會感到麻痹和刺痛
And you will slowly asph_iate until you choke to death...
你會慢慢窒息死亡…
while remaining fully conscious, unless you do exactly what I say.
除非你按照我所說的做
I will die before I compromise my county.
我會在損害國家名譽之前死去
We will drive you to your office...
我們會到你的辦公室去…
where you will write a letter on official stationey...
你要寫一份官方文件…
denouncing the treatment of women in Iran.
公開譴責在伊朗的女性醫療待遇
Then you will get your antidote.
然後就會給你解藥
That's it?
就這些？
伊朗大使館,倫敦
How may I help you?
我能幫你嗎？
我想到伊朗避難
Dr. Bailey, my apologies for the delay.
貝利教授，我為事情的延誤道歉
Professor Dombrovski has declared the weapon authentic.
鄧布拉斯教授已經檢測了武器
And we're prepared to proceed.
我們隨時可以發射了
As soon as my money's transferred, Mr. Ambassador.
等我拿到我的錢，大使先生
Move! She's with me.
滾開！我們的人
Arman?
阿曼？
He needs to go.
他得離開這裏
Okay, okay.
好，好
What are you talking about? Who is she?
你在說什麼？她是誰？
Sir, I'm sorry, you need to leave.
先生，抱歉，你得離開了
You need to shut up!
你給我閉嘴！
No.
不
What is happening here?
這裏怎麼回事？
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
Tell me what is happening here! Who is she?
告訴我怎麼回事，她是誰？
Get out! When I say "get out", get out of here!
當我說『滾出去』！你就該滾出去！
You need to go!
你得走了！
You shut the fuck up!
你媽的閉嘴！
Where's the safe?
保險櫃在那裏？
What?
什麼？
Where's the safe?
保險櫃在那裏？
Poo poo is coming.
便便就要爆發了
24 Hour Plumbing.
24小時服務
Hury. Emergency.Water everywhere. Come quick.
快點，水管破了，快來
Stop! Plumbers, wait!
站住！等等！
It's okay! This way.
沒事的！這邊
Money received.
錢收到了
Good show.
幹得好
Let's see our friend here.
來看看我們的朋友
Would you lend me your knife, please?
你能借我刀子嗎？
Thank you.
謝謝
sorry about the mess on the carpet.
抱歉弄髒了地毯
Oh well.
哦，對了
At this point, Jack... You don't mind me calling you "Jack", I hope.
從現在開始，傑克，我希望你不介意我叫你『傑克』吧
You must be beginning to comprehend...
你必須意識到,,,
the stunning totality of your failure.
自己的失敗了
You can't give it to them.
你不能給他們
I've no more interest in giving Red Mercuy to these boys...
我沒有興趣給他們的…
than I have in giving it to you.
我會給你的
Jesus.
天啊
Yes, it's a sad old world. Anmay, that's only my opinion.
在以前那個悲慘的世界，這只是我的想法
But the central point is this...
但是重點是這個…
when men like you and those dickheads from MI6...
當時像你一樣的MI6小雜種…
or CIA or whatever sewers you came from.
那些CIA人員，或者其他為你做事的人
When you take away not only my life...
當你們不但毀了我的生活…
but the innocent lives of my dear beloved wife Natasha...
奪去我心愛的妻子娜塔莎的無辜生命…
and my little boy, who was only 6.
及六歲的兒子
What can I say?
我能說什麼？
When you mess with me, buddy...
你膽敢惹我，小子…
this is what you get.
你會付出代價的
Go to hell, old man.
去你的，老傢伙
Fare thee well, patriot.
再會了，愛國者
Boom.
砰
Now what's ne?
下一個是？
Ah, Washington.
華盛頓
Baby, hey.
寶貝，嘿
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
Awesome!
真厲害！
Oh shit.
天啊
Is that it?
就這樣？
It's counting down, Frank.
開始計時了，法蘭克
Shut if off.
把它關了
Shut Yeah. With what? Acupressure?
關掉，用什麼關？氣功？
I don't know.
我怎麼知道
Why is it my responsibility?
為什麼是我的責任？
Just do something.
做點什麼
With my Mr. Chemisty set?
我的化學很爛？
I don't know what I'm doing.
我不知道我在幹什麼
You want me to push a button?
你要我按這個按鈕嗎？
Bailey's loose and the bomb's ticking.
貝利不見了，炸彈計時中
Wait. Excuse me, ma'am.
對不起，女士
Hello, I have an appointment.
你好，我有預約
Gun!
有槍！
Get that bomb outta here.
把炸彈拿遠一點
Drop it now, darling. That's right.
放下，親愛的，對了
My gun!
我的槍！
Press the button. Ground floor.
快按鈕，下樓
Marvin, let's go!
馬文，快點！
Jolly good show.
很好玩
Bollocks.
去你奶奶的
You really drive this ridiculous thing?
你會開這荒唐的東西嗎？
Can you shoot?
你會射擊嗎？
We need eyes, Francis.
我需要指引，法蘭克
Come on, Frank. 40 minutes.
來吧，法蘭克，剩40分鐘
How ya doin' back there?
怎麼樣了？
I can't talk to you right now.
我現在不能說話
How is it?
如何呢？
It's fine.
非常好
Shit!
操！
Show me something.
秀給我看看
Victoria...
維多利亞…
I got eyes on. Bailey's heading for the M4.
我看見了，貝利正要去機場的路上
Got it.
明白
Got it!
知道了！
This one should stop it and this one should detonate it.
這條剪了會停止或者爆炸
It's fifty fifty.
各50%的機率
Wait!
等等！
That's weird.
不對勁
Do you have any idea what you're doing?
你知道自己在做什麼嗎？
Wait, wait!
等等！
Stop cutting wires!
停止剪那些電線！
I knew we were gonna die!
我知道我們都要死了！
Ready to kill this son of a bitch?
準備好殺掉這賤人了嗎？
Abso bloody lutely.
隨時準備著
Damn it!
媽的！
Trouble.
麻煩了
Marvin!
馬文！
It's 2 pedals and 2 sticks.
需要兩腳踩踏板，兩手握控制器
Okay.
好的
Damn it! We missed him. He's going into the airport.
見鬼，追丟了，他朝機場去了
Go get him!
抓住他！
Where are you?
你在哪裏？
In trouble.
有些麻煩事
Turn back! You are in restricted airspace.
飛回去！你在禁飛區中
They're gonna blow us outta the sky.
我們馬上要在空中爆炸了
I wouldn't wory about that.
我一點也不擔心
The engine's shutting down.
把引擎關掉
Mayday! Mayday!
求救！求救！
Frank!
法蘭克！
I knew we were gonna die!
我知道我們要死了！
This is your last warning!
這是最後的警告！
Please, tell me you're not crashing with a weapon of mass destruction.
拜託告訴我，你們不是帶了，大規模殺傷力武器墜落
No, Frank, no.
不，法蘭克，不要啊
Oh God.
天啊
You okay back there?
你還好嗎？
It wasn't exactly a three point landing, Frank.
如果正確著陸多好，法蘭克
How's the bomb doing?
炸彈怎麼樣了？
I can't stop it.
我無法停止它
We gotta get it outta here.
我們要離開這裏
Hey!
嘿！
Get outta the car.
下車
Hello, Frank.
你好，法蘭克
Welcome aboard.
歡迎登機
Always the good soldier, aren't you?
你一直是個好士兵，不是嗎？
Stalemate.
僵持狀態
How will you take him out...
你要如何救他出去…
and not shoot her first?
而不會打到她？
Frank, it's okay.
法蘭克，沒事的
You can shoot. It's okay.
你可以開槍，沒事的
Put the gun down.
放下槍
Put the gun down!
放下槍！
Drop the gun!
把槍扔一邊！
Put the gun down, Frankie.
放下槍，法蘭克
Thank you.
謝謝配合
Pretty smart.
很聰明
So love does conquer all.
愛能征服一切啊
Go to your golden warrior.
你到那邊去
That's a good girl.
好女孩
Come here.
過來
It's so sweet.
真感人啊
Now leave the plane. Take Nightshade with you.
現在離開飛機，帶著那個炸彈
Bye, Frank.
再見了，法蘭克
Sweet dreams.
做個好夢
Why didn't you just shoot me?
你為什麼不開槍？
What happened?
怎麼了？
I couldn't disarm it.
我不能停止倒數
Crap.
喔，見鬼
Marvin...
馬文…
it's going to detonate?
快要爆炸了嗎？
Yeah.
是的
Put your arms around me.
抱著我
Oh...
啊…
I didn't see that one coming.
我怎麼沒預料到這個
There's something you don't see evey day.
這種事不是每天都看得到喔
You put the bomb on the plane.
你把炸彈放到飛機上了
And you didn't think to mention that?
而你提都不提一下？
You blew up my plane.
你炸毀了我的飛機
sorry.
抱歉
I was wrong? So we're not even gonna die?
我錯了？所以我們死期還未到嘛？
Not yet.
還沒到
I was actually starting to like you.
我甚至開始喜歡你了
I was even thinking about not killing you.
我也許不想殺你了
This is what happens when you Ty to save the world.
就在你試著拯救全世界時
You can't put a price on these things.
你不能計較這些
You owe me 30 mil for the plane. And 20 for not killing you.
你欠我三千萬的飛機，和讓我不殺你的二千萬
You're a dead man, Moses.
你已經死了，摩西
Thanks for your help.
謝謝你的幫助
Really.
真的
You think he means it?
你認為他是認真的？
Nah, he's a nice guy.
不，他是個好傢伙
I mean it, Frank!
我說真的，法蘭克！
All right.
好吧
They're going to be right as rain.
他們做得對
He made the run to emotional safety.
他尋求他的精神慰藉
So...
所以…
I did hear about this job in Caracas.
我聽說在加拉加斯有份工作
And?
然後呢？
Don't look at me. She's your girlfriend.
不要看我，她是你的女朋友
Come on.
走吧
超危險特工2 狠戰